User Stories

As a job seeker 
I want to see how much tax I pay 
so that I can work out how much I can save per year.


As a landlord 
I want to see how much tax I pay
So i can plan my tax affairs

As someone who want to retire
I want to know when I can retire
So that I can have a goal


Potential tables...
2 thoughts.. all assets, jobs etc can be thought of as streams of cash. however they require carying info to determines what they mean. Could be stored in a single mega table but could get messy.


User
PAYE Salary
Private Pension
Public Pension
Umbrella salary
Dividend income
Family?
